thesupercars.org 2019-02-27

# Privacy Policy - The Supercars - Car Reviews, Pictures and Specs of Fast, New & Used Cars

By using **Thesupercars.org** , you are agreeing to abide by its Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use. **Thesupercars.org** may collect some personal information about you, such as an email address, mailing address, username and password. You knowingly give us this information when you comment and by doing so, you are allowing us to track your use of this web site and relate it to the information that you have provided. If you wish to be notified of the use of such tracking software and/or disable such software, your browser may offer this feature by means of its options or preferences menu.

The Personally-Identifying information mentioned above may be used by **Thesupercars.org** to enhance or personalize your experience on the site. This includes the promotion and marketing of products that may be of interest to you. Your use of this web site is consent to the foregoing use of your Personally-Identifying Information by **Thesupercars.org**.

**Thesupercars.org** may also share any of your Personally-Identifying Information with select companies or organizations for their own marketing and promotional use. While **Thesupercars.org** wishes to only share your Personally-Identifiable Information with such companies that follow the appropriate privacy policy procedures, it can bear no responsibility to what these said third parties will do with the information. If you wish that we not share your Personally-Identifying Information with third parties, you may "opt out" by emailing us with a request pertaining to such.

You should be aware that any Personally-Identifying Information, such as your user name and email address, as well as any other information that you post on a bulletin board, commented on a blog post, or otherwise specifically and knowingly disclose by use of the forums, may be directly collected and used by third parties.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy atÂ <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>
